- Did you know
that businesses report significant improvements
in decision-making and advanced data analytics?
Learning these skills can increase your efficiency,
making you an invaluable asset.
Hi, I'm Walter Shields.
As a best-selling author of the number-one book on SQL
and a LinkedIn Learning instructor
have helped thousands of learners transition
to data analytics and data science.
Over 250,000 learners have completed
my SQL Essentials Training Course,
and many have asked for the next step.
Well, this is it,
a course designed to elevate your SQL skills.
In this course,
you'll gain hands-on skills
to design efficient and scalable database schemas,
create automated ETL processes for data handling,
improve query performance with indexing and partitioning,
and write advanced SQL queries for deep data insights.
So get ready to transform your skills
and unlock new opportunities.