- [Instructor] For this course, here's a heads up
on what you should know.
There are a number of exercise files
accompanying this course,
and most of them come in two versions,
a completed version,
and an incomplete template with just instructions.
Now this setup is designed to give you the flexibility
to choose your own learning path.
You can start by referencing the completed version,
which I will be using in the course,
and this allows you to see the end result
and understand the goal before you try your hand at it.
Alternatively, you can begin with the template
and use the completed version to check your work.
In addition to these files,
there's a completed database file
that includes all the queries
I'll be demonstrating throughout the course.
This resource is invaluable for verifying your progress
and making sure you're on the right track.
The primary objective of this course is for you
to design and build a database from scratch.
That being said, I highly recommend taking the approach
of building the database step by step
as you watch the videos.
This hands-on method will give you a competent grasp
of the skills and something tangible
to show when you're done.
By the end of this course,
you'll have built a fully functional database
showcasing your new-found skills.
So dive in, stay engaged,
and let's make this an amazing learning experience.