- [Instructor] In front of you
is the full list of exercise files
that accompany this course.
Now, throughout the course,
I'll be indicating when you should reference
each of these files to enhance your learning experience.
As you can see, we have the template and complete files.
We also have the raw CSV data files.
We have the completed database file
and the ETL pipeline script file.
Now, to get these files downloaded to your machine,
here are the steps you take.
First, go to the Related to this course area,
then click on Show all next to Exercise files.
Click Download next to the zipped file.
Once this file has downloaded to your computer,
go to the location where you've downloaded it to,
right-click to unzip the contents of this file.
If you are on a Mac like myself,
you would need to double-click
to unzip the contents of the file.
Once it's unzipped, then you go to that unzipped folder,
and there you'll see the full list of files
that you see here displayed in front of you.
Now, these files are key
to your hands-on learning experience,
and as I mentioned, you can choose to start
with the completed versions to see the final result,
then work with the templates
to practice and solidify your skills.